ManyChat is a software that's a partner
with Meta,
and it allows you to set up automation so
you can respond to people that
comment.
You can set up automations to people
that engage with your
content. Now, first thought, golden rule,
do
not DM people cold. Do not do that.
There's this
notion that if someone follows you online
that you should send them a DM.
Absolutely not. There
are some people out there,
in a bid to do lead generation,
are messaging strangers in a bid to spark
up
conversation. Do not do that. There
are people out there that when
you follow me, they then follow you
and say, "I've seen that you follow
James Smith.
Are you interested in talking about
workouts?" Absolutely not.
What we're talking about with ManyChat
is that if you give someone a prompt
and you
give someone a little
ask of something to do, that they do it,
and you can send
them an automated message. Now, this
is going to be
so we can get to a place of something
that I call the post and ghost.
Now,
there's a full course to this in the
description.
There's also a little offer for anyone who
has been kind enough to come to
this live stream. But a post and ghost
is pretty much this.
Let's say before bed tonight,
let's say I've got a campaign,
let's say I need to
get email addresses, whatever it is,
I should be able to put
that post out there,
and every post is a digital asset
that you put out on the internet,
and it performs
for you. It's going to get pushed
and shown to people.
Hopefully, this video in weeks
and months' time,
the algorithm's going to keep
putting it in front of people,
and it's going to keep churning leads
and core sales
or whatever it is.
For you guys on Instagram,
you want to be able to put a post out
before you go to bed,
and you want to be able to wake up
and for there to have been
some meaningful change.
And I'm not talking about people saving
the post.
I'm not talking about people liking
or commenting.
I'm talking about either money in the bank
or even better, email addresses in
your database. So, to put it this way,
this
year I had a single carousel post on
Instagram that
netted me 15,000 emails, 12,000 of
which were from Instagram and
about 3,000 of which were from Facebook.
It was a carousel post with about 10
different pictures, text overlaid,
and from
that I said to people
if they commented a certain word,
I would follow up with
them,
and that gave me the opportunity to send
them a little DM and say, "Hey, I'm
on a mission. I want to do this.
If you click this link,
we can do a sign-up." Now,
some of you might be wondering why we
would even do this in the first place.
So, think of it this way.
There's four pillars
that I'm always preaching about
online. And for those of you just joining,
feel free to use the comments, feel free
to ask away. We're going to get into
that in a second. My four pillars
are this.
The first one is social media,
where we are right now, for instance.
Pillar one,
we need to create good content,
we need to be engaging, we need to have
a finger on the pulse of problems
that people are having.
So I have an inclination, a feeling
that people are struggling
with getting from social media to data.
That's why I created this course.
It's why I've put
that link in the description.
It's why I'm doing this webinar on a
Sunday evening.
So I know that people
are struggling to get people's email
addresses.
So that social media part here,
you can make amazing content,
you can go viral, but
if you're unable to get someone's data
or email address, you
are unable to go from
stage one to stage two. Now, quickly,
although this video is not about it, from
getting someone's email address,
we probably want to nurture them in some
kind of
email marketing sequence,
or we want to broadcast some kind of
newsletter
to the point that we can take them to
stage three.
Stage three would be sending them to a
sales page where there's a very clear and
obvious offer in front of them.
So just go through again.
Social media, obtain the email address.
Email address,
send them to a landing page.
Landing page, very clear offer.
From there,
we would then want them to go to stage
four, where they become a client.
So with those four stages, the purpose
of this video is to help people understand
that the problem most businesses
are facing is going between stage one
and two, and chatbots help
solve that problem.
They help solve the problem by giving
people
an opportunity to take the conversation a
little bit
further, but better yet,
to do the one thing
that most of us struggle to do
online,
and that is to take someone away from
social media.
And although the DMs
that we're going to
are still on their social media,
it's a very competitive place,
the swipe algorithm.
They're on an explore feed.
They're in bed. They're doing whatever.
They're going, boom, dopamine, dopamine,
dopamine, dopamine.
For us to have the opportunity to just put
a little message into their DMs, even if
they can't access it then,
they can come back to it later, which
is another very
powerful thing.
Because even a lot of the time people go
to your landing page, they
don't buy.
A lot of the time people look at your
stuff and go, "Wow, that's
amazing," but they don't do anything with
it.
But you sending that DM means that even
if they're busy and they're about to catch
a train or they're going on a date
or they're about to go back into work,
later
that night, they can go back to that DM.
They can reactivate, re-engage with it,
click on the link, go visit your landing
page again.
I don't know what it is,
and I've worked with probably over 1,000
businesses now.
When you tell someone to click the link in
your bio, it's a bit like, "I don't work
for you. What?
You're telling me what to do, bruv?
Shut up.
I'm not doing it." Click the link in my
bio. Click the link in your bio.
But by saying to someone, "Oh,
DM the word cat," or actually
if any of you want to
see this in action,
on my James Smith business page,
for those of you
that didn't do it already, if you
were to go onto my most
recent post.
Actually, not the most recent post,
the one that says DM the word woof.
So if you actually want to see this in
real life, guys, you're going to go to the
James Smith business page. Cor,
my autofocus is a madness there.
I've got to cover my face. There you go.
And if you comment the word woof,
you'll actually see a real-life automation
happening. Now, 30 people from
that commented the word woof
instead of DMing it,
and I'll explain why that
was an issue in a second.
But that puts people onto an automation
where I can just quite well and show you
everything that this is capable of.
You're probably wondering why on a live
stream I would tell you to do that, and
it's for the exact reason
that I just spoke about.
I said that if you were going to go away,
be busy, and do something else, it would
be good if there was a DM
or a message there with the link
that you could refer
back to. And for any of you that do
message me the word woof on my James Smith
business page, not my James Smith main
page, may I add,
you have a link there so that
if in tomorrow, a week, a month,
you're like, "Oh, do
you know what?
I actually want to set up that," you can
go back to our
conversation,
and you'll see the messages
that I've sent you. Cool.
Now,
the next thing we probably need to talk
about is ManyChat has
got a lot of different functions.
But even before we get into
that, and again,
if you have any questions,
put them into the side.
I'm going to answer them all in a second.
Second of all,
if you do want to access this course,
there's a link in the
description.
There's also an offer For any of you
that might be
considering working with me.
Not in this chat, Henry.
Calm down, mate. What
are you trying to do, mate?
It's been a long weekend.
First thing we need to talk about before
we go into all the different amazing
things that ManyChat can do
is where do we send that person?
This is a question old as time. Epictetus,
Plato,
Socrates, they're all saying,
"Do I send someone to my landing page?"
Now,
if we go back to the four-stage system,
and I know I use this all the time,
getting someone to do business with you
is very similar to having sex with
someone.
Now, I know a lot of you
are going to be like,
"I don't know this four." Stage one
would be putting yourself on a dance floor
or going to a bar, going to a club,
whatever it is.
If you're not in the right place,
AKA social media, it's going to
be very,
very difficult to get the attention
that you need to move down the stages.
So then
stage one would be that.
Stage two would be asking someone for
their number.
Now, we must appreciate
that out of 10 people
that we got to in real life, maybe
only one of them would give us their
number.
Someone might not be interested,
someone could be married,
someone could be in a
relationship, someone might not trust you.
There are plenty of reasons.
And if you were to get one in 10 numbers
on a night out, you'd be, "Well, that's a
pretty good statistic." But
when we look in the realm of, "Oh,
I only got 10
email addresses from a post
that got 1,000 views," it's the exact
same.
You can't expect everyone to give you the
bloody number. Cool.
So then when we've got someone's number,
we then need to decide what are
we going to do with it?
And the number represents email marketing.
Because if you want, you could just say,
"Hey, babe, do you want to bang?
Do you want to do the hot, wet,
sticky stuff?
Do you want to go Netflix and chill?
Do you want to go [imitates sex] ?"
And most of the time, they're
going to say no. It's not
that they don't want to have sex,
because if they didn't
want to have sex,
they would've never given you the number
in the first place.
It was you just did not go through the
stages necessary for courtship,
for chivalry, for being a gentleman,
even though this course is fine for women,
too.
There is a certain amount of processes
and decorum that one must
attain to in order to get the sale. So
you could just get their email address,
boom.
Or you could even get them on your
chatbot, boom. Send them to your website.
Buy my shit. But
sometimes they're not nurtured
or warm enough.
They need to be taken for a couple of
drinks, maybe a couple of dates, maybe a
Nando's. I'll get this, babe,
but you're only having two regular sides
because I'm
not a mug.
I'm not a mug. And
if we're getting an ice cream on the way
home, we're going
50-50,
right? Instead, it'd be better off to say,
"Hey,
I'm going to approach you.
I'm going to get your number.
Then I'm not going to spam you.
I'm going to sensibly message you.
And rather than going for the kill,
rather than send you straight to the
landing
page, I'm going to get your email address,
and we're going to nurture." Because
when we take people on dates, we
are nurturing the lead.
And if we push too hard,
they're going to push us back.
Every warm-blooded male knows in this live
stream
right now that if you try
and sleep with a girl on a first date,
she's making you
wait till date five.
But hypothetically speaking,
may I add, if you
were to be a gent on the first and second
date,
that action could be happening a bit
sooner. That's all I'm saying.
So we get the email address.
We then want to nurture.
Now,
there should be some kind of value given
with that.
If you're going to get someone's email
address, don't just try and sell to them.
And again,
we could get into the email marketing
course for that.
Then further down the line,
we would want someone to do a sale with
us.
But the stages from one to four probably
look at 20% of your total
following should be in your email list.
So if you've got 1,000 followers,
you should have 200 of those on your email
list.
If you don't,
you need to be working harder to convert
your existing followers to
give you their email address,
not so much growing your profile.
From there, an open rate of 50%
is pretty good.
Now, when it comes to conversions, it
is very difficult to say because I don't
know
your product, I don't know your offer,
I don't know how in demand your offer is.
I don't know how good your followers
are because if you get all your followers
doing recipes and then you're selling a
workout plan, you're not going to get the
conversion rate of someone else that's
selling a recipe book. Does
that make sense?
So,
the next thing we need to think about
is ManyChat has got
many different things on there,
on the website that you can do,
and it's very
overwhelming. And the first day
that I used ManyChat, I was like, "Oh,
I'm going to
have a mental breakdown.
There's too much here." I actually went to
upwork.com.
I was like,
"Maybe I can hire someone to help me
navigate this."
But very simply,
there's only really two things
that you're going to want to use on
ManyChat,
a DM prompt and a message prompt. Now,
these prompts are set up from Instagram or
Facebook. Someone either comments on it--
I'm going to actually share my screen
and show you some of it in a second.
But, yeah,
I would say get people to comment on your
post.
If they comment on your post,
you can send them a message back.
But if they DM you, as any of you
that would have DM'd my business page
saying,
"Woof," you'll notice
that you can put multiple replies with
multiple different
ways to multiple avenues to get people to
do stuff.
So you could say
that it's easier to get someone to
comment, but if you can get
someone to DM you,
you can really open stuff up.
So another benefit of using ManyChat
is that you can integrate team
members into your backend.
So for any of you that are using setters
or closers in your DMs, using ManyChat,
you can kind of give someone a backdoor to
access your DMs without giving them the
keys to the castle as far as
access to your Instagram.
Hmm.
[bottle opening] Noatonic Focus Blend,
getting the job done.
We're going to get into some of the
questions, and I might
share my screen with you in a second.
Physio Clark, "I'm a physio.
I have an email list.
I use ManyChat to get them through to
providing me their email address,
but I'm not
sure the topic is niche enough.
Should I niche down as a physio?" It
depends on
what you're selling. I would say what
are you selling, mate?
Because if you're selling just
physiotherapy, it's a bit bland,
it's a bit broad.
But I'm going to make this up,
and I'm going to be crass for the sake of
being a live stream.
If you had a back pain program
or a shoulder mobility
program or a thoracic rotation program,
I would work backwards from
that program. So let's say
you were selling a thoracic rotation
or extension program for people that might
have limited overhead. I'm making this up.
You could then say, "Right,
my email responder
is going to be 30 ways in 30 days
that you can
loosen up your back, or
that you can get better back rotation,
or you can improve
your golf swing, or you can
reduce the chances of shoulder injury,
or whatever." Then I would have content
specific about that.
So the content would then say,
"If you're someone that can't
do this, someone can't do that,
someone can't do this,
then I recommend you do
these three things. And by the way,
if those three things help, I've created a
30-day series that's completely free.
You give me your email address via the
chatbot, and we'll get into it." You email
them every day with an actionable thing
that they could do or something that they
didn't know,
or some kind of fact about the anatomy of
the thoracic or
whatever. Then towards the end,
maybe after day five, you start saying,
"By the
way, I've got a paid program. By the way,
I've got a paid course.
By the way,
I've got this." Then I would sell them
into something specific from
that. But if you're just a physio going,
"Oh, if you want physio tips, sign up,"
and then, "Oh,
if you want to hire me as your physio
online," I don't think you
should niche down to a certain cohort of
people.
I think you should niche down to a
problem.
Again, so many personal trainers are like,
"Yeah, I work with
21 to 40-year-old men." I'm like,
"Fuck you. Fuck you.
No,
you would work with a 20-year-old."
And they're like, "Oh, they're a bit
immature." I'm like, "Fuck off. If
that 20-year-old had money,
you would fucking work with them full time
if you wanted." If the sheik
of a fucking region in the Middle East
was 19 and wanted to
hire you and send you out on a private
jet, you're going to go, "Nah, mate.
Come back in two years." Shut your mouth.
Same when they say, "Oh,
I work between 20
and 40-year-olds." So a 42-year-old
comes to you as a successful business
owner. It's bollocks.
You're just saying shit. So
that niching stuff fucks me off.
When people are like,
"I work with busy parents," why?
Just work with adults, bro. All adults
are busy. And guess what?
A parent has got some stuff going tough
for them. But you know what?
A nurse has also got the same struggles.
So I hate it when people pigeon in on the
exact same
things when you could easily just broaden
out.
Like me with my business mentorship,
link in the description.
I'm not like,
"I work with 22 to 43-year-old
left-handed English people
that live overseas." Because it doesn't
matter. Instead, I work with people
that have a specific problem.
They're struggling to make content online.
They're not very good at getting people's
contact information from people that
follow them online.
They're not very good at creating sales
pages or conversions or
coming up with offers. They're the things.
Now, if you're an accountant, cool,
I can help.
If you're a physio, I hope I can help.
If you're a PT or whatever it is,
I would like to niche on the problem,
not necessarily niche on the
person.
Rule the Trainer,
"What email software do you recommend?"
Well,
I use several as your email list grows.
MailChimp, I'm not a fan of.
It's just a bit shit. I love AWeber.
It's basic as. Klaviyo, very good as well.
For our fitness app, we use SendGrid.
I've never wanted to go to SendGrid,
but my business partner made me do it.
Okay. John,
"I left you a comment on your last video
on how to improve your stream
quality. Hope it helped."
I didn't see it, brother.
But
what
could be better about this, mate?
And I know you're probably thinking, "Hey,
brother,
you could be streaming in 4K."
When I stream in 4K, it crashes.
I tell you what, if you can email me,
james@neutonic.com, that'd be amazing,
actually.
But I've had to dial down the stream
quality
because it's been causing me a madness.
Quality Antics, "Join the mentorship.
Loving it so far." Thank you.
"I'm helping businesses with video
content.
Loving your Discord reviews and feedback.
Thought on solid lead magnets I could be
using with ManyChat."
So you say here that you're helping
businesses with video content.
You're saying yourself
that you love my reviews.
So why not do reviews, post the reviews,
and say, "If you want your content to
be reviewed,
leave the comment the word review." Then
you could send them a
form going, "Hey,
I would love to review your content.
Here's a few things I need.
Name, email address, phone number,
URL of your socials."
Then they have a little tick box
that says they're happy to go for
marketing.
They do that. Wallop.
Into the lead magnet they go.
Into the reviews.
And you can even just say, "I'm sorry,
but I can't do 100% of the
reviews."
Okay.
"I work with UK top physios." Okay.
You guys, stop talking to yourself.
Ollie Staniland, "Like that.
Niche to a problem,
not an avatar." That's a flipping video,
mate.
That's a fucking video.
Ashley,
"Should you put a limit on how valuable
you should make the lead magnet?
I.e.,
is there such a thing as making it too
good?"
No. And you know what?
Think about this.
I'm willing to give you every single thing
that's in the course in this live
stream, because imagine if I
was to sit here and go, "Oh, I'm going
to convince people to buy my course today
on ManyChat, but
I'm not going to tell them much about it
so they buy the course." That
wouldn't work because there wouldn't be
enough value in that.
So instead,
I'm way better off sitting here for maybe
an hour and
giving you everything, and then
if you bought the course and you're like,
"Oh,
you told us most of
that on the live," you're hardly going to
be pissed off because
it's a value equation of getting the
information from me.
So
imagine it's like not trying too hard on a
first date.
You should be doing everything you can in
your content to get people to give
you their email address.
You should be emailing them as well as you
can and using
the best lead magnet as possible because
you want to be flipping impressive,
because actually, the reality
is for a lot of us in business,
and it's going to be
sad to admit this,
I should teach you 95% of the stuff
that you need to know before you pay me.
That might sound weird, me saying that.
When you pay me, it's more so
that now we have to do it
because you've given me the money.
I can sit here till I'm fucking
red in the face saying,
"Post more content, do this,
do that." So actually,
95% of everything
that I'm going to teach you guys
is pretty much free online.
The next 5%,
you pay me the few thousand dollars.
You wake up tomorrow and you go,
"Holy shit,
I need to do this now."
And then I nurture you through the bits
where you have the
panics and you have the setbacks
and you have the highs
and you have the lows.
When you do really well, I'm like, "Cool,
get the fuck back to work." When you have
a bad day, I'm like, "Cool,
get the fuck back to work."
And it's actually those
things that help people more so.
Harrison Fernandez, cool name.
When your potential leads go through your
email campaign and don't sign up, how
frequently should you keep emailing them?
Buy or die. That's what I say.
Buy or die, motherfuckers. Buy or die.
I will keep peppering them, and
if they buy, cool, and if they don't,
they're out.
Some people out there have got an email
list of 3,000 people, and they're like,
"Oh,
I don't really email them because I don't
want them to unsubscribe." I'm like,
mate, brother, do me a favor.
If any of you out there have got an email
list of
3,000 people that you haven't touched in a
year, keep emailing that list until it
whittles down to 500.
Because let me tell you this,
when you whittle down an email
list from fucking 3,000 to 500,
you're going to make a few sales out of
it.
Then the people that have left, fine,
cool.
Then when you've whittled down your email
list and it becomes really, really
small,
do you know what you're going to wake up
thinking?
"Fuck me,
I need to grow my email list." Perfect.
So, it's one of those things where,
yeah, pepper the fuck out.
They can always unsubscribe.
Nima, getting sales directly from YouTube,
but would you still recommend the email
nurture? Yes. Because
so far on my YouTube,
the most a video's made me
is like $12,000, $13,000, but my email
marketing has made
coming up to a million dollars just from
emails.
So if you said to me, "James,
would you rather
have $1,000 from this video today,
or would I rather
have 100 emails?" I'd way rather have 100
emails.
I can make so much more money from 100
Because we have a Black Friday sale for
Neutonic, email them.
We fucking do a business mentorship
discount,
like the link in the description.
Boom, email them. We have a new product,
email them.
We have an event going live in Dubai
and Sydney, email them.
With an email, I can do so much. Now,
the one thing I would say is
there is a gray area here,
something that we can co-navigate.
There is an Uno reverse plus four that has
arrived here.
Sometimes it's good to have a
low-ticket course, sell something for $99,
because then you can do both.
Then I get your email address,
and I also get you to purchase something,
and I
also get you into the ecosystem.
So out of the
ManyChat and Chill
course that's in the description,
whoever buys that, they'll buy it, they'll
implement it, hopefully they'll do well.
By the way, all of you on this course,
if you buy that and you don't love it, you
can just email me and I'll refund you.
I'm confident there's going to be enough
people that go, "That's exactly what I
need." Anyway, but then out of those,
you're probably going to get
eight to 10% of people upsell.
So, yeah.
Sometimes you can get the email address
from selling to them in the first place.
Loving the content.
Was looking at jumping in the mentorship,
saw this live with
the offer. Bosh.
Mm.
And I'll tell you this.
There is an offer in the description.
However, I do sometimes find this snakey.
So if you bought a mentorship subscription
from
me in the last
three months, and you're now seeing
that I'm doing it at a cheaper rate,
I'll meet you at the new rate.
I'm not going to stand that someone
yesterday would've paid more. So
if you bought yesterday
and you paid a bit more
than that offer, just email me
and I'll refund the difference,
because that's just
something that I stand by.
Now, okay.
Fate, running one-to-one contest prep,
physique coaching.
Look to level up our social email
marketing.
Kyle, can I ask you, are you in Australia?
Your name looks familiar.
Running one-to-one contest prep,
physique coaching.
Looking to level up our social email
marketing. Do love that.
Are you in Sydney by any chance? Just
answer me that, Kyle.
It could be someone different.
Could be someone completely different.
Jane, thanks for your business mentorship.
I'm not maximizing what I use,
but the goal-setting session means I know
what I'm
moving on to next time. I'm a wills
and probate lawyer, still relevant.
Yes, I would think so.
I would like to know a little bit more
about that. And again, here's one for you.
If any of you are in, let's say,
a wild niche.
So let's say you're a wills
and probate lawyer,
or let's say you're a dog trainer,
or let's say you're something a bit left
field, and you join my program, and you
get to the point where you're like, "Mate,
I was hoping this would work, but it's
not." Again, I'll refund you.
If you come back in six months and go,
"Hi, mate, I'm a bit skint.
Can I have my money back?" I'm going to
tell you to fuck off.
But if in three to four weeks time you go,
"Hey, mate, I thought this would work
for my business, it doesn't." Anyway,
I'll do it.
Are brain capsules going to be restocked?
Yes, very soon.
I think they should've been already.
Fade and Fortune.
I decided to create a moving Berlin guide
and
follow up with monthly newsletter,
and three posts this month for ManyChat.
I've got 1,000 subscribers. That is class.
I don't really know how to monetize it
now. Any tips?
So those 1,000 subscribers,
are they on your email list
or on the ManyChat
database?
Because if they're on your ManyChat
database, there's not a lot we can do
with them because of the legislations
and all kinds of things that are
going on with that.
But did you get them onto an email list?
And if not, why not, can I ask? So,
yeah, get back to me on that. Ryan,
that's a gangster move.
Not many course providers would do
that on price. My pleasure.
I just don't want to be that guy.
Pretty much that's it. Daniel, come
and see you in Dubai.
Habibi, I'll see you there.
Harrison Fernandez, the cool name, bro.
If a lead signs up through an email
campaign,
do you have automations to remove
them from the campaign
or leave them in the campaign?
Then if they quit,
do they automatically get added back in?
No.
So if someone unsubscribes,
all email marketing platforms work the
same way.
You have to give people the opportunity to
unsubscribe.
You can't send email marketing campaigns
without that.
Now, if someone unsubscribes, they're out.
Now, some people would like to,
or they set it up so that if people
buy, they're removed from the automation.
We're moving into email marketing.
Oi, you cheeky bastards.
We're supposed to be talking about
chatbots.
But I will let it slide. Now,
if you have an automation set up that
if someone
doesn't buy, there
is a trigger to then offer them with an
email at the end of the
automation with a discount,
you would want to remove them.
But if you've got a value-based email
marketing subscription,
whatever it is,
that's just firing daily fucking banter
or knowledge or whatever it is,
if that's just do, do, do, do, do,
that's going in
all the time, then you could potentially
have it where you just keep them into the
automation. Okay.
Used to live in Sydney,
currently living in the UK,
doing the digital nomad
traveling coach thing now. Kyle,
did you have a pop at me
about six years ago
about GVT?
I did a post about German volume training,
and I think you
had a little pop at me on Facebook.
Is that you?
Because I'm a bit of an elephant, mate.
Now, I could be wrong,
but I see your name.
I see your name and it's taking me back.
I never forget a face.
When we do the live events,
people introduce themselves, I'm
like: "Mate,
I've been critiquing your content for the
last three months.
I know who you are."
But there's just something... Anyway,
we'll get back to it. You let me know.
I joined, less money I've spent.
Can see why you keep doubling the price.
Thank you very much.
I do keep doubling the price.
I'm not apologizing for that either.
I do feel like a fraud most days,
but still, people are doing well,
so it's all
right. Anima The Machine,
biggest mistake you see online marketers
making
that's stopping them making money.
Biggest mistake you see online marketers
making that's stopping them making money.
Hmm.
It sounds crazy.
This is what I'll answer it.
There's too many people doing things
online with themselves in mind,
not their client.
So for instance,
a lot of coaches want people to buy six
months in advance or to show
commitment of at least 12 weeks.
Now, that's cool,
but that's not for your client's
commitment. Don't say that.
That's bullshit.
What you're saying is,
"Give me your money up front, so
if you leave, I'll make the
money." But if you
were thinking of your client first,
you would let them pay
weekly or at least monthly.
Then marketers as well, like with
Nutonic, I said to people, "Buy a case,
and if you don't like the
flavor,
I'll send you another flavor." Because I
know, as a consumer, your
biggest worry is not liking the flavor.
That means we essentially won't make any
money from you until you buy two or three
more cases. But I kind of know that
if I think about the consumer in mind
and do things like that,
they will buy two or three more cases.
But if someone buys a flavor
and they don't like it, and we say,
"Sorry, unlucky,
buy another one," that's not thinking
about the consumer first.
So every single decision that you have,
even on this Live, the fact that I've
offered people their money back,
the fact that I've said to people that
if you paid
more last week,
I'll see you the difference.
Everything has to have the consumer in
mind, because if I think about your needs
and wants more than mine,
I'll do really well.
And that's the thing
that I don't think a lot of people kind of
realize.
If I can always just continually,
and you as a marketer,
think about the person
that is in front of you with the problems,
if you just put them first all the
time and make all your decisions based
around that,
you're going to come across better than
your competitors, which is what marketing
is.
Caleb, any update on Nutonic coming to US?
Yes, we started formulation last Monday,
so we're going to produce in
Brisbane.
Now, pretty much, we had concerns
that the ingredients
that we had in Nutonic
wouldn't be allowed to be sold in
Australia.
We've been given the green light.
We're going ahead. We're doing it.
And if there are any problems in the
future, we can deal with that once we're
in production. So yeah,
we're probably going to do tropical
and orange to launch,
but it depends on the flavors
that we get back.
We're probably 15 weeks away from it,
I'll be honest.
Hmm.
The sachets and the pills you can get,
they just take ages in shipping.
For that, I apologize. And if you
are in Sydney, and you
see me in my car, shout at me
and I'll give you some stock.
I always keep some.
I didn't put them onto the mail list.
I'm new to this stuff.
I'm not sure I'd do that yet. Okay,
Fate and Fortune.
Whenever you get someone through to
ManyChat,
the first thing you need to do is
give them a link to take them somewhere.
James, getting that veiny bicep,
loving the input.
Testosterone replacement, hell of a drug.
So yeah, Luke, I think I followed
that GVT.
Yeah, I'm just sure, Kyle,
that back in the day, there
was a bit of
back and forth.
Yes, bro. Yes. Did I? That's gold.
I'm sure we crossed paths.
Fitness First, Bondi Platinum.
I remember it, mate.
So you were triggered. In your video,
you alluded something on the leg press,
and I was
anti-GVT,
and you said I didn't know what I
was on about.
You think I was going to forget that?
You think I was going to forget that,
Kyle?
I don't forget that. Yeah, bro,
because I was thinking, I'm going
to see this guy in Fitness First,
but from what I remember, you
had a very big back squat. So about
that time, I started training jujitsu,
and by the time we crossed paths again,
I had my black belt.
So I'll be ready, you big-legged fuck.
You think I'd forget about that,
having a pop at me? But it's all right.
We go full circle. We're back here.
We're friends now, okay?
Joshua Williams.
Wanted to thank you for motivating me from
move to Spain to
Australia. I'm glad you're here. Faye,
saw your Instagram story on weekly
check-ins
being useless.
Now you should be checking in daily.
How would you manage this as a solo
business owner?
Weekly check-ins creates a glass ceiling.
So first of all, with clients,
fuck doing a weekly check-in.
Imagine this,
most of your clients don't want a
fucking weekly check-in. They don't.
They just want their fucking program
and to get the result
that they're paying you
for. Guess what? You're going, "Oh, fuck.
I've got to catch up with Jenny at 3:00
p.m.
on Th..." She doesn't want to do the
fucking weekly call.
I never did a weekly call. Now,
with my business-to-business clients,
I'm going to try and show you
if this tanks the Live and
this ruins my livestream,
thank you very much for coming.
There's links in the description.
But if I can do the entire screen
and
share. Oh, actually,
let's try doing a window.
Maybe we go
over to-- Let's try this for a sec.
Okay. Wow. So this was the thing
that I wanted to show you guys.
So for ManyChat,
this is the first thing we'll look at.
Oh, you bloody...
Hopefully,
it won't show my password to everyone.
That'd be embarrassing.
Okay, here we go. So we
were talking about using ManyChat before.
I actually might as well just show you
here.
So
very quickly, these
are some of the automations
that I've been running.
You see this one from yesterday, worth
494 people have done it,
and 33 people commented.
Now, I'll just show you very quickly,
I set up this automation so that if
they did the wrong thing, I said, "DM me,
not comment.
Can't you bloody read,
you from Essex?" And if we go down here,
we can just see
some of these are getting pretty good
click rates.
So considering this is just a post
that says content,
332 people,
then if they end up clicking on this,
they get sent through to the landing page
for content mastery.
So this is, again, a landing page,
which is going to be a good place to sell
someone to get that. So with those things,
the content mastery side of things
are great.
Now, going back to what you
were saying before, you
were asking about doing
check-ins. Now,
I still don't like doing hourly calls
with everyone,
and I'll explain why in a second.
I can't fight, I'm just big,
so I'm screwed.
Jumping into the mentorship,
super keen to level up content in my
marketing.
And yeah,
is the ManyChat course in the mentorship?
It is.
Okay, I'll actually show you now.
Kyle,
I'm glad that we've become friends again.
So [chuckles] I'll give you
a little sneak peek now. So if we go to
here, if I type in
ask the wrong one.
So if we go into the mentorship,
I'm just going to show you
the kind of things that you get.
Oh my god, this is
long.
Oh, I'll do it after.
You basically get the suite of all courses
that I've created and
all courses I'm ever going to create.
So once you guys sign up,
you get access to everything
and everything that I'm
going to add. Now, the one thing
that I was saying about keeping up with
people would be this. So this is my
Discord. So these
are some of the things
that I've been sharing with people.
Rather than me doing weekly calls with my
clients, or the call we're doing right
now is just for you guys,
because here I will chat to
people all the time. So today,
we're going through different concepts for
YouTube.
We're looking at thumbnails,
we're looking at packaging,
and our BJJ course.
We've got people here
that have trained jujitsu with
me. If we look at growing socials,
we're kind of just
hashing stuff out.
And some of these conversations,
we need back and forths.
So for me,
I would much rather do two hours a day in
here with people,
helping them, retaining clients,
share your business, Q&A.
So this is where we spend most of the
time, because the reality is,
if I just did
one of these calls for all my clients
every week,
it's going to be very difficult
for them to be able to communicate all of
the problems they're having and me to
get back and communicate with them.
We've got 70 people on right now,
and even then, it's quite hectic.
So if there are hundreds of people here.
So I would say not everyone wants to do
that call, if that makes sense.
So instead, is there a way that you can--
arguably in the Discord,
I'm saving time as well, because
when someone asks, other
people are watching.
Okay, Simon.
Thoughts on applying these systems to real
estate photography services
in London. Again, first of all,
real estate is amazing because people want
to see inside other people's houses.
Good photography and videography
is important because real estate agents
need that.
So I think the content side could be
interesting.
Then you could create a worksheet of 22
biggest mistakes
that real estate agents are making,
taking pictures of property.
Get real estate agents to sign up to your
email list,
sell your services to them.
So I think it could.
Boom Weight Loss.
After four years working face-to-face,
launched last week online.
20 awesome clients my first six days.
Email list a priority. That's great.
Love that. Joshua. Main channel video
was a life changer.
Feeling like a sunflower in the shade.
Love that. John Isaacs.
Email sent. Let's fix your stream.
Thank you. I know the colors
are a bit out.
I'm filming in auto.
Okay, as a follow-up on this,
is the ManyChat course the mentorship?
Yes, it is.
All the links you need
are in the description.
Do you think it's better to use ManyChat
on carousels or reels? Okay.
I would use them on both. And carousels,
guys, are probably
your secret weapon to getting conversions
from your existing
audience.
So if you do a carousel with no music,
it gets slammed to your existing
following. You put music on,
it goes a bit wider.
But honestly, once in a while, reel,
do a carousel post, put a bit of story in,
get a good hook on that first
tile,
and you can get so much data from people.
Paul Alima did one this week,
and it absolutely crushed.
Christoph.
Launching a math teaching website to sell
lessons for teachers.
I have 200 plus. Should I launch now
or wait till I have 400 made?
Launch now, brother.
If you wait till you're ready to launch,
you launch too late.
David.
Went to your business mentorship in
London. We spoke one-to-one.
Made my first TikTok the next day,
haven't stopped.
I'll be emailing you on Utonic personal
mail after this live with an update.
Love to see it.
How about YouTube monetization?
Have you already been paid by YouTube?
I don't even have monetization on for this
channel because it would
be,
what? $1,000 a month? Cool.
I'd rather people didn't watch
adverts.
My main channel can do a few grand a
month, but for this one, I haven't
even turned it on because I can't be
bothered. It sounds bad.
I'm going to say it.
I'm here to make real money.
$1,000 from YouTube, I'm not interested.
Keep your money, YouTube.
Keep the AdSense. I'm not interested.
I'm here for the real money.
I like Discord back and forth.
Doesn't waste time,
helps with asking the same questions,
and also when I'm in the
Discord,
I can easily spot trends of things
that are doing well and
things that potentially aren't.
So yeah, for me, I just like Discord.
I think it works.
I think it works well for the people in
there.
Last couple, Sean, Shawn, Shaun?
I coach founders.
Responsibility, guilt, stress, pressure.
They rarely engage publicly on socials.
No like, share, but DM, it kills reach.
How do I fix this? But DM, it kills reach.
How do I fix this?
I don't understand what you're asking.
They rarely engage publicly on socials,
but DM
Well, they could still DM you from a post.
You could still have a mini chat.
Fucking,
"If that sounds like something you'd be
interested in, do this." But if
you know exactly who it is,
if you coach founders,
that sounds like quite a niche.
Maybe just message them on LinkedIn
or pay someone to do outreach for you.
Caleb: "Love your content creation course.
Great info for $99.
What camera are you using now for this
stream?" Oh, brother.
We've got a Sony FX3.
We've got a 30-millimeter lens.
I didn't know any of this stuff until
about a year and a half ago, by the way.
We've got an ND filter on,
which isn't doing much because I'm filming
in auto.
Then I've got a Sennheiser MKH 416 out of
shot.
And I've got my main light here,
giving me a bit of Rembrandt.
Got a hair light here.
And I've got a bit of a globe bulb here.
This studio only cost £35,000 to build, so
the camera wasn't
that expensive in comparison,
but you don't need all of this.
Some of my streams
that made me tens of thousands of dollars
were on a £500
camera. So, like a Sony ZV-E10. But yeah.
All right.
Harrison: "Usually post parkour content.
Should I keep posting my coaching videos
to that page?" Well,
if you're a coach,
unless you're coaching parkour,
no,
because you're just attracting the wrong
people. I've said this again.
If you wanted to grow your email list
and you offered everyone
that joined a free
mug, would it be a good idea?
Probably not, because everyone
that joined probably
just wanted a free mug. And
if you're trying to sell something to
someone, you
don't want a list of people
that just came for the mug.
Faye: "So if you have clients,
you wouldn't do check-in forms to make
sure they're
making progress and accountability.
Just chat group would be enough?"
In some cases, what I would do is,
with my clients is I'd say, "Message me
if you
need anything,
and update me on your progress." I'd get
them to come to me
every
however long.
And they'll let you know
if they're not making
progress, because they'll be like, "James,
it's been two weeks.
My weight hasn't moved." "James,
it's been two weeks. I've lost this.
Should I change my calories?" So you
should be in contact with them.
I just don't think you need-- For me,
putting something in my fucking diary
at 3:00 p.m.
on Wednesday throws off my whole week.
I'd much rather just chat to people,
but that's my approach.
Math website follow-up. Pricing model,
monthly, yearly membership versus selling
individual lessons.
I would offer everything
and see what's most popular.
"Thanks for this session, James."
Legendary energy always sparks ideas.
Thank you.
Jayden Lee:
"What contributes to an effective lead
magnet?" This is going to be the final
question. This is a very good question,
Jayden.
Basically, you're going to spot a problem,
a reoccurring problem, and you're going
to create a solution for it. So
then you just have to reverse engineer the
lead magnets.
One of my favorites was
that landing page asset that I did.
People were really struggling with how
they should set up a landing page.
Was like, "Cool,
I'm going to print out what looks like a
really good landing page,
and I'm going to get people to sign up for
it." But, okay, the best way to explain
this, I would say,
is every time a problem arises, try
and create a lead magnet,
but don't just put all your eggs in one
lead magnet.
Create five and see
which one performs best.
And then you go, "Oh,
when I physically held something
and held it in front of
people,
it performed better." So then the next
five all have to be things that you
can physically hold or show people
or have a visual prop.
And over time, they get better
and better and better and better.
I think volume is going to be everything
when it comes to lead magnets.
It's only when you've done 20
or 25 of them that you know what's worked
best.
Thanks for tuning in. There
is a business mentorship offer in the
description.
I'm going to delete this video in 48
hours, so that's going to be gone.
And there is also the $99 chatbot course.
If you don't love it, drop me an email.
I'll refund you in full.
But the fact of the matter is,
you know you need to get using it.
That's what the resources are for.
Thanks for tuning in.
Catch you guys in a bit.
If you can't be good, be careful.
Bye-bye.